legalbuds.com 2013-11-22

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy   
GLE / legalbuds.com   
http://www.legalbuds.com

General Information   
GLE / legalbuds.com takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following information to learn more about our privacy practices. 

  * This policy covers what personally identifiable information GLE / legalbuds.com collects and how it is treated. Personally identifiable information is information that can be used to identify visitors to the http://www.legalbuds.com Web Site. This information may be limited to an IP address or extend to personally identifiable information such as your name, address, email address, or phone number. 
  * This policy only applies to http://www.legalbuds.com and does not extend to the practices of other Web Sites that we may link to, companies that we do not own or control, or to people that we do not employ or manage. 

* * *

Contact Information   
We invite you to contact us if you have questions about this privacy policy. 

Our Internet address is located at [http://www.legalbuds.com](http://www.legalbuds.com/)

**GLE / legalbuds.com  
Box111 325 E Jimmie Leeds Rd. Suite 7   
Galloway 08205   
NJ USA **

You may contact us by e-mail at [globallifesupport@gmail.com](mailto:globallifesupport@gmail.com)   
You may contact us by phone on 1-866-HERBS-4U 

* * *

Dispute Resolution   
GLE / legalbuds.com is committed to resolving any dispute you may have regarding our privacy policy quickly and efficiently. 

Disputes will be handled by our customer service representative. Our customer service will promptly correct any errors.

Please e-mail us at: globallifesupport@gmail.com file a complaint about this sites privacy policy. 

* * *

Information Collection   
When visiting Web Sites certain information about you and your computer can sometimes be collected. This section explains what information GLE / legalbuds.com collects, and how it is used. 

Information Collected \- What information do we collect and why? 

We collect the following identifiable information about our visitors:

    * user.name    _(optional)_
    * user.home-info.online.email    _(optional)_
    * user.home-info.postal    _(optional)_
    * user.home-info.telecom.telephone    _(optional)_
    * user.bdate 
    * user.gender    _(optional)_
    * user.business-info.postal    _(optional)_
    * user.business-info.telecom.telephone    _(optional)_
    * user.business-info.online.email    _(optional)_
    * dynamic.clickstream 
    * dynamic.http 
    * dynamic.clientevents 
    * dynamic.searchtext 
    * dynamic.interactionrecord 
    * dynamic.miscdata 
  
We collect identifiable information for the following reasons: 
    * Web Site and System Administration 
    * Research and Development 
    * Contacting Visitors for Marketing of Services or Products 
  
For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes NO information regarding the domain or e-mail address. We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations. The information we collect is used for internal review and is then discarded. With respect to cookies: We use cookies to record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart and record affiliates sales if a sale has been made via a link from an affiliates website.. If you supply us with your postal address on-line you will only receive the information or merchandise for which you provided us your address. Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line. With respect to Ad Servers: We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies. Upon request we provide site visitors with access to transaction information (e.g., dates on which customers made purchases, amounts and types of purchases) that we maintain about them, contact information (e.g., name, address, phone number) that we maintain about them , or a description of information that we maintain about them. Consumers can access this information by e-mailing us at the above address or writing to us at the above address. Consumers can have this information corrected by sending us e-mail at the above address, calling us at the above telephone number, writing to us at the above address. With respect to security: All Finanicial details and ordering information is stored on 3rd party SSL secured servers that are individually inspected and approved for such activity. None of your details are stored on our servers.

Our Web Site generates server log files automatically. These log files are used to generate statistical information and error reports to ensure the Web Site runs with a minimum of disruption. They are not actively used to identify individual visitors.

* * *

Information Recipients \- Who has access to the information collected?   

    * Ourselves and/or our entities acting as our agents or entities for which we are acting as an agent.   

* * *

Information Retention \- How long is this information retained?   

    * Stated-purpose  

All of our legal bud products are 100% natural and contain only organic smokeable material.   
None of our products will cause you to fail a drug test. Do legal buds get you high?   
None of our products are sold as marijuana alternatives, legal weed, or alternatives to illegal street drugs.   
By purchasing from legal buds you agree that you are atleast 18 years of age.   
Our legal bud products are available in better herbal smoke stores nationally and across the world.
